Finding Aid for the Clara Hieronymus Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Clara Hieronymus Papers
2008
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0627
46.25 linear feet
Inventory Completed 5/6/2008
- Slide Show of Egypt (Box 1)
- Rameses II Talk March 24 and 26, (1987) (Box 1)
- Description notes of Egypt Slides (Box 1)
- Horus Vol 4 No 2, (1986) (Box 1)
- Touchstone Number 9, (Winter 1987) (Box 1)
- Al-Ahram, (18 June 1987) (Box 1)
- Press Release Rameses the Great, (1987) (Box 1)
- Museum of Cheops Boats, (1987) (Box 1)
- Smithsonian, (April 1986) (Box 1)
- Newspaper Article Ramseses II (Box 1)
- Cairo Marriott Hotel (Box 1)
- USA Today Wednesday, Feb 25 1987 Memphis, TN (Box 1)
- Info on Rameses The Great Exhibition in 1987 (Eugene Watts) (Box 1)
- Passport El Gezirah Sheraton Hotel (Box 1)
- Egypt (Hotel Mena house Oberoi) (Box 1)
- Egypt and Travel to Egypt (Box 1)
- Sayed Kammel Lamlon (Rent Cars) (Box 1)
- Ramses II folder (Box 1)
- Egyptian Mail Saturday, January 17, 1987 (Box 1)
- Cheminement du Futur, Janvier 1987 (Box 1)
- Islamic Cairo Mosques of Salah At Din (Box 1)
- Rameses The Great Memphis and Egypt, Jan 11-18 1987 (Box 1)
- T.s.m.v Bacchanal (Box 1)
- Transair (the TAA Magazine) (Box 1)
- The Sydney Morning Herald Monday, June 6 1977 (Box 1)
- Smile, hey The Cairns Post, June 10, 1977 (Box 1)
- Connair Celebrates Alice to Carnes (Box 1)
- Islamic Cairo Mosque of Salah (Box 1)
- Cata Tours Central Australian Tours Association (Box 1)
- Ayers Rock Mt Olga National Park (Box 1)
- Sydney tourist guide (Box 1)
- BPA Day Tours (Box 1)
- Queen and Me/Sydney mine car crashes (Box 1)
- Obadiah West’s Bar & Grill (Box 1)
- Melbourne Leisure Time (Box 1)
- The New Zealand Herald (Box 1)
- The Northern Territory of Australia (Box 1)
- Hotel Southern Cross (Box 1)
- Aborigines, 1997 (Box 1)
- Australian Tourist Commission (Box 1)
- Sendale Hearing on Canal Open with Vance (Box 1)
- Aussie Trekker Lost Dog (Box 1)
- One foot in fish (Box 1)
- Lizard Island (Box 1)
- Paronarma Guth (Box 1)
- Katherine- Nature’s Wonderland (Box 1)
- Where (Sydney’s guide) (Box 1)
- Aboriginal Basket (Box 1)
- Perth’s Sheraton Hotel (Box 1)
- Imperial Palace (Box 1)
- Mississippi Arts Pavilion (Jackson, Mississippi) (Box 1)
- Travel (Arts and Leisure) (Box 1)
- State/metro (Box 1)
- Southern Style (Box 1)
- Palace of St. Petersburg (Box 1)
- Tour of Palaces St. Petersburg (Box 1)
- Color in the Court (Box 1)
- Letter to Clara Hieronymus (Box 1)
- Mississippi Public relations tourism (Box 1)
- Greek Brochure (Box 1)
- Town & Country (Box 1)
- Notes about St. Petersburg (Box 1)
- The man who would rule Russia (Box 1)
- Herald Tribute (Washington Post) (Box 1)
- The Gatchina Palace (Box 1)
- Discovering St. Petersburg (Box 1)
- The St. Petersburg Press, August 22-28 1995 (Box 2)
- St Petersburg (Box 2)
- Notes Catherine the Great (Box 2)
- Russia Photos (Box 2)
- Continue-Russia Photos (Box 2)
- Style (New York Times) (Box 2)
- Southern Accent, November-December 1994 (Box 2)
- Mississippi University for Women (Box 2)
- Hotel Astoria, 1912 (Box 2)
- The State Museum (Tzarsko Jeselo) (Box 2)
- State Hermitage, Summer 1995 (Box 2)
- Delta Plane Tickets and Travel Writer (Box 2)
- Satarrsmith (Box 2)
- Proof of story, Russia (Box 2)
- Notes on Russia (Box 2)
- Map Minolta (Box 2)
- Delta State University (Box 2)
- Palace of St Petersburg (News Release) (Box 2)
- New York Times, September 10 1995 (Box 2)
- Hammer explains why country museum won’t get his art (Box 2)
- New York Times Nov 22 1987 (The Region: the city casts its Theaters in Stone) (Box 2)
- Phantom of the Opera (Box 2)
- China’s Modern Masters (Box 2)
- Art People (New York Times) & Drama Award (Box 2)
- Play writers (Box 2)
- Reviews of Musicals in 1987 (New York Times) (Box 2)
- Classical music Symphony reviews, USA Today, Dec 15 1987 (Box 2)
- Review of movies, Broadway, and art from the New York Times, 1987 (Box 2)
- Entertainment reviews by the New York Times, February 12 1998 (Box 2)
- Stage reviews New York Times, 1988 (Box 2)
- Entertainment Reviews, 1987 (Box 2)
- Arts/Entertainment NYT, 1987 (Box 2)
- She’s the Top by David Sacks (Box 2)
- Peter G Davis “Seeing Stars” and NYT Music Reviews (Box 2)
- Notes on a book, “chess” (Box 2)
- Endangered Classics (Box 2)
- Arts/Entertainment NYT, 1987 (Box 2)
- Box office results (Box 2)
- NYT Writer dies (Box 2)
- TV & fashion from NYT articles (Box 2)
- B’way Shrugs off Wall Street (Box 2)
- Theater Review (Box 2)
- Art, Music, leisure, 1987 (Box 2)
- Guide to London’s Rare Book (Box 2)
- Entertainment/Book reviews, 1987 (Box 2)
- Entertainment News, 1987 (Box 2)
- Entertainment News, 1987 (Box 2)
- Politic, 1987 (Box 2)
- Entertainment museum article, 1987 (Box 2)
- Schiller Theater (3rd draft) (Box 2)
- Clara’s 3rd draft (Box 2)
- Pictures (Box 2)
- Pictures 2 (Box 2)
- Pictures 3 (Box 2)
- Pictures 4/slides (Box 2)
- NYT, 1995 (Box 2)
- Smithsonian & Modern maturity (Box 3)
- Traveler (Box 3)
- Museum Notes (Box 3)
- Trans-Balkin Tours (Box 3)
- Tennessee Humanities Council (Box 3)
- Christopher Columbus News Paper (Box 3)
- Wonders (Box 3)
- Sadberk Hanim Muzesi (Box 3)
- King Midas/ Turkish Reflections (Box 3)
- Sultan the statement (Box 3)
- News notes/ American Theater Critics Association (Box 3)
- Science Time NYT, 1993 (Box 3)
- Turkish Daily News, 1991 (Box 3)
- Splendors of the Ottoman Sultans (Box 3)
- Kultur Bakanligi (Box 3)
- Istanbul Intrigue (Box 3)
- Turkish Stuff, 1991 (Box 3)
- Istanbul/Art (Box 3)
- Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 3)
- Exotic Istanbul (Box 3)
- Thank you letter and Ottoman Pamphlets (Box 3)
- Metropolis/ new classicism (Box 3)
- Letters to Clara Hieronymus (Box 3)
- Show guide (Box 3)
- London (Box 3)
- Reserve a box for the interval (Box 3)
- News from Britain (Box 3)
- London Shopping Spree (Box 3)
- London Theatre (Box 3)
- London Post (Box 3)
- Art Treasures from China (Box 3)
- News Notebook/London News (Box 3)
- Equus (Box 3)
- Clive Barns (Box 3)
- Show Abroad (Box 3)
- London/university of London (Box 3)
- Globe Theatre (Box 3)
- London/winter festivals (Box 3)
- London Theatre flights (Box 3)
- London this month (Box 3)
- Tennessean, 1965 (Box 3)
- Books (book reviews) (Box 3)
- Requiem for a nun, article, books, 1970 (Box 3)
- Letters, 1970 (Box 3)
- The Nashville Tennessean- letters (Box 3)
- Berlitz Translation Service (Box 3)
- Review of Requiem of a Nun (Box 3)
- William Faulkner Article (The Oxford Eagle part II ch. 3 section 1 (Box 3)
- Notes and the john Golden Theatre (Box 3)
- Book Ch. 3 Section 1-3 and Ch 4 Section 1-4 (Box 3)
- News release and incorporated new page (Box 3)
- Letters and more scripts (Box 3)
- Faulkner’s play Requiem for a Nun (Box 3)
- Strange and Incomprehensible, Faulkner (Box 3)
- Chronology (Outline of Requiem’s development) (Box 3)
- Incorporated material for Requiem (Box 3)
- Requiem of a Nun (Box 4)
- Dallas Theater Center (Box 4)
- Thomas Y Crowell Company letter to Clara (Box 4)
- Requiem draft part 1 (Box 4)
- Requiem draft part 2 (Box 4)
- Requiem draft part 3 (Box 4)
- Random Requiem papers (Box 4)
- News Articles about Clara (Box 4)
- Clara letters (Box 4)
- The Nashville Tennessean Aug 21 1970 (McCartney letters) (Box 4)
- The Bolivar Commercial (Box 4)
- 1100 Broadway (Box 4)
- Hieronymus and News articles about Requiem (Box 4)
- Clara Hieronymus letters (Box 4)
- Dear Mrs. Izard letters (Box 4)
- Izard and Hieronymus letters, (1970) (Box 4)
- Various letters about Clara’s book, (1971) (Box 4)
- More letters (Box 4)
- Clara Hieronymus (miscellaneous) (Box 4)
- Adventure Theatre’s in school players (Box 4)
- Plays (Tom Sawyer and Snow White) (Box 4)
- CTC (Children Theatre Center) (Box 4)
- Just So Stories (Box 4)
- Academy Theatre and Eisenhower High (Box 4)
- School Theatre (Box 4)
- More reviews (Box 4)
- Newspaper/ New York Time, 1974 (Box 4)
- Handwritten Notes (Box 4)
- Stuff by William Glover (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous stuff (Box 4)
- Various Critical Reviews (Box 4)
- News clips and critics (Box 4)
- Envelope from Tennessean to Clara (Box 4)
- News articles about Clara and Faulkner (Box 5)
- Hieronymus Papers (Box 5)
- Leila Papers (Box 5)
- Clara notes (Box 5)
- London 1 (Box 5)
- London 2 (Box 5)
- News articles on Broadway (Box 5)
- National News Story (Box 5)
- Theatre Reviews (Box 5)
- The Theatre (Box 5)
- Reviews (Box 5)
- Tennessean (Art Galleries) (Box 5)
- Presidency and the Arts (Box 5)
- Cancer Society (Box 5)
- Tulsa (Box 5)
- Oklahoma (Box 5)
- Transformagic (Box 5)
- Newspaper clips and letter to a legislative member (Box 5)
- Tulsa Area (Box 5)
- Calendar (Los Angeles Times) (Box 5)
- Theatre Review (Box 5)
- Notes and Walter Kerr Script (Box 5)
- Agencies and Radio Out (Box 5)
- Jack Gaver UPI Drama Editor (Box 5)
- November 1972 (Box 5)
- Internal Review (Box 5)
- 1940s (Box 5)
- Wiggins (letter to Wiggins) (Box 5)
- More 1940s (Box 5)
- Clara 1930s (Box 5)
- Letter to Lois (Box 5)
- Letters from 1947 to 1949 (Box 5)
- Critique (Box 6)
- Information Bulletin (Box 6)
- Les Fourberies Descapin (Box 6)
- Children’s Theatre Company (Box 6)
- The Theatre (Box 6)
- A solo (Box 6)
- Various Theatre Article (Box 6)
- Day Press Collect (Box 6)
- Assisted (Box 6)
- Saratoga Festival (Box 6)
- The clam made a face (Box 6)
- Delegate Addresses (Box 6)
- Children Theatre (Box 6)
- Clara Hieronymus Letters (Box 6)
- Yearwood and Johnson (Box 6)
- More letters (Clara) (Box 6)
- Letters (Box 6)
- Clara Hieronymus letters (Box 6)
- Theatre critics (Box 6)
- School/Children’s Theatre (Box 6)
- Montreal/Moscow/Theatre (Box 6)
- Letters (Box 6)
- More letters (Box 6)
- Clara Hieronymus letters (Box 6)
- Stage strike (Box 6)
- A chorus line (news article) (Box 6)
- Letter file part 1 (Box 6)
- Letter file part 2 (Box 6)
- Letter file part 3 (Box 6)
- Picture and letters (Box 7)
- Letters (Box 7)
- Letters in a London Shopping Guide (Box 7)
- Christmas letters 1, 1960 (Box 7)
- Hieronymus letters, 1960 (Box 7)
- Letters, 1961 (Box 7)
- Children’s Theatre, 1962 (Box 7)
- Formal letters, 1960 (Box 7)
- 1961 letters (Box 7)
- stuff, 1976 (Box 7)
- The freedom forum at Vanderbilt (Box 7)
- Personal letters (Box 7)
- The Chicago market daily (Box 7)
- Letters 1970 and 1971 (Box 7)
- Christmas card and The best of John Simmons (Box 7)
- News articles, Jan 23 1972 (Box 7)
- Letters general (Box 7)
- Film criticism in the news during the 1960s (Box 7)
- Clara’s Mail (Box 7)
- In the news (personal stories) (Box 7)
- Handwritten letters (Box 7)
- Cuna Indian art (Box 7)
- Articles Faulkner and the Swan Ball (Box 7)
- London (Box 7)
- Daily Express, (1974) (Box 7)
- Public relations/ Nashville (Box 7)
- Royal Academy Schools (Box 7)
- The Tennessean, 1970-1972 (Box 7)
- Letters (Box 7)
- Plays/Superstar 1100 Broadway, 1972 (Box 8)
- Letters (Box 8)
- Letters/postcard (Box 8)
- Thank you letters (Box 8)
- Clara Hieronymus letters (Box 8)
- Television letters (Box 8)
- Mrs. Clara Hieronymus (Box 8)
- Business letters (Box 8)
- The Tennessean, 1973 (Box 8)
- Better living (the Tennessean) (Box 8)
- WYT and Entertainment (Box 8)
- Simon cured/movies (Box 8)
- Clara’s Sunday Column (Box 8)
- Theatre 370 William Glover (Box 8)
- New York Times, 1975 (Box 8)
- Variety (1975 Criticism of musicals) (Box 8)
- African-American Theatre (Box 8)
- Theater 430 Ly Mary Campbell (Box 8)
- Theatre (news) (Box 8)
- Broadway (news articles) (Box 8)
- Museum and art (Box 8)
- Stage view (Box 8)
- Broadway (Box 8)
- Musical reviews (Box 8)
- Fair and lovely (Box 8)
- Photos and letters (Box 8)
- Tennessean (Clara), 1968, 1969 (Box 8)
- 1974, 1976 Tennessean (Box 8)
- Miscellaneous (Box 8)
- 1972 awards (Box 8)
- London-Marquis (Box 8)
- New York Times (Artists) (Box 8)
- Disney, 1974 (Box 8)
- Elegant Accessories (Box 8)
- News articles abut lifestyle (Box 8)
- Luxury (Box 8)
- Theatre flight membership list (1976) Clara (Harpeth Hall) (Box 8)
- Artist and photo (Box 8)
- Mail/handwritten letters (Box 8)
- The Nashville Banner (Box 8)
- Biography of plays (Box 8)
- Globe Theatre (Box 8)
- Association Espanola de Teatro Para la Infancia (Box 8)
- Cancer, 1947 (Box 9)
- More cancer, 1947 (Box 9)
- 1947 (Box 9)
- Social problems (Box 9)
- War, man power commission (Box 9)
- Louis Thomas and Stuff from, 1947 (Box 9)
- Politics, 1947 (Box 9)
- Labor Laws (Box 9)
- Magazine articles (Box 9)
- Advertisement (Box 9)
- London crushed bond (Box 9)
- Tulsa (Box 9)
- Tulsa (Box 9)
- Mexican in the Southwest (Box 9)
- Scholastic Notebook (Journal) (Box 9)
- Clara Wiggins (Box 9)
- Random Clara stuff (Box 9)
- Ways a means for extending and expanding (Box 9)
- Local Health (Box 9)
- Broadway play guide (Box 9)
- Kerr and culture (Box 9)
- Theatre (Box 9)
- Theatre and library (Box 9)
- Broadway box office (Box 9)
- Theatre box scores (Box 9)
- Galactica (Box 9)
- Lainie Comes Home 350 4 takes, total 1,310 (Box 9)
- Shubert Empire, (Wednesday, Dec 27, 1972) (Box 9)
- Times Square (Box 9)
- News, 1972 (Box 9)
- Shakespeare (Box 9)
- December 1973 (Box 9)
- New York Times, 1974 (Box 9)
- News New York Times, March 1974 (Box 9)
- Clive Barns (Box 9)
- Reviews (Box 9)
- Literati (Box 9)
- Musical by Mary Campbell (Box 10)
- Addat End off Broadway (Box 10)
- Variety, July 1974 (Box 10)
- New York Times, June-July 1974 (Box 10)
- Huxtable, Barnes, Kerr, Dr. Armand Hammer (Box 10)
- Canaday, Glover, Kramer (Box 10)
- Variety and New York Times, 1974 (Box 10)
- More New York Times and Variety From, 1974 (Box 10)
- Arts and living (Earning Gap Hits performance arts) (Box 10)
- News, 1972 (Box 10)
- Travel, Theatre Flight (Box 10)
- St. Patrick’s Cathedral (Box 10)
- Membership list #2 (Box 10)
- Variety, 1971 (Box 10)
- Theatre Schedule and News (Box 10)
- A preview of a new Broadway…, October 1972 (Box 10)
- A New York Times, 1973 (Box 10)
- The Theatre Reviews (Box 10)
- Reviews of Cliver Barnes (Box 10)
- City Hall by ADA Huxtable (Box 10)
- William Glover (Box 10)
- Clive Barnes (Box 10)
- Walter Kerr (Box 10)
- Jack Glover and William Gaver Various reviews (Box 10)
- Immediate Release (Clara Bloom) (Box 10)
- News from, 1971 (Box 10)
- News, 1972 (Box 10)
- Artrs/Theatre reviews, (1971) (Box 10)
- American Express News (Box 10)
- Picture of Clara and Le petite Salon Script (Box 11)
- Company letters to Clara (Box 11)
- 1981 Tennessean Article mentions Clara (Box 11)
- Various letters to Clara (Box 11)
- Letters to Clara from early 80s (Box 11)
- Letters to Clara (Box 11)
- More letters to Clara (Box 11)
- Handwritten letters (Box 11)
- Handwritten letter through the years (Box 11)
- Two Clara letters (Box 11)
- Editorials (Tennessean) (Box 11)
- Personal letters (Box 11)
- Personal letters 2 (Box 11)
- 1964 Tennessean “Goldwater Victory sure” (Box 11)
- The book of Job (Box 11)
- News articles 1961 and a picture with Jamie Marsh (Box 11)
- Articles about Clara (Box 11)
- 1949 resignation of Clara (Box 11)
- More articles about Clara (Box 11)
- Clara photo/ news clips (Box 11)
- The Tennessean, 1988 (Box 11)
- Tennessean 1950s and 60s (Box 11)
- Articles about Clara and a letter (Box 11)
- Letters (Box 11)
- Personal letters (Box 11)
- Clara letters (Box 11)
- Thank you Clara letters (Box 11)
- Community Theatre (Box 11)
- Dental Health week (Box 11)
- Clara letters (Box 11)
- Clara Hieronymus Christmas Cards (Box 11)
- To Clara Hieronymus (Box 11)
- Clara letters (Box 11)
- Clara Hieronymus letters (Box 11)
- Newspapers of Clara (Box 11)
- Tulsa Magazine (Box 11)
- Profiles (Box 11)
- Theatre (Box 11)
- Correspondence (Box 11)
- Nashville, Tennessean, 1954 (Box 11)
- News, 1955 (Box 11)
- S.C. Hieronymus (Box 11)
- Script (Box 11)
- News articles from, 1955 (Box 11)
- The Tennessean, 1955 and 1956 (Box 11)
- Art and Drama Column (Box 11)
- New York Times 1956 Art write-ups (Box 11)
- Journal articles on Art (Box 11)
- More Art Journals articles (Box 11)
- Art Journal articles (Box 12)
- New York Times Art 1950s (Box 12)
- Art Criticism (Box 12)
- Article by Clara and New York Time’s article from the 1950s (Box 12)
- Picasso (Box 12)
- Tennessean, 1957 and 1958 (Box 12)
- Tennessean, 1957 (Box 12)
- The Tennessean More from, 1957 (Box 12)
- Artists (Box 12)
- The critic on the hearth (Box 12)
- Art and Art criticism (Box 12)
- New members (Box 12)
- Random Clara (Box 12)
- Clara the critic (Box 12)
- Criticisms by Clara (Box 12)
- Riverfront (Box 12)
- Letters from the 1980s (Box 12)
- Various plays (Box 12)
- The year, 1983 (Box 12)
- Curtain time 1 (Box 12)
- Curtain time 2 (Box 12)
- Theatre (Box 12)
- News from 1988 & 1989 (about Clara) (Box 12)
- Theatre stuff (Box 12)
- The park London hotel (Patrick Connolly) (Box 12)
- Speech given, March 2, 1967 (Box 12)
- Tennessee performing arts center (Box 12)
- The third dimension, 1970 (Box 12)
- Letters and Larry Peabody (Box 12)
- News 1990s (The Tennessean) (Box 12)
- Clara letters (Box 12)
- (Clara Hieronymus’ talk on Catherine), 1990-1991 (Box 12)
- Magazine (Box 12)
- 1971 Clara in the News (Box 12)
- Scripts (Box 12)
- Nashville performances 1990s (Box 12)
- Letters, 1974 (Box 12)
- Pictures (nature) (Box 12)
- Accolades (Box 13)
- Theatre and Art presentation (Box 13)
- The Tennessean, 1964 (Box 13)
- Photos (Box 13)
- The Tennessean, 1974 (Box 13)
- Letters to Clara late 1950s (Box 13)
- Clara’s C.V. as of 1980s (Box 13)
- Random Clara stuff (Box 13)
- Rhode Island College (Box 13)
- “Never too late” and talk on furniture (Box 13)
- Scripts (Box 13)
- V.A. sued and better living article (Box 13)
- Random articles (Box 13)
- In the news (Box 13)
- Notes (Box 13)
- Better living pictures (Box 13)
- Is photography art (Box 13)
- The art of the possible (Box 13)
- Peer review (general comments) (Box 13)
- Design (plays) (Box 13)
- Home decorating (Box 13)
- The many worlds of music (Box 13)
- Travel (exhibits)—home decorating (Box 13)
- Glitz confession (Box 13)
- Acuc AA bulletin (Box 13)
- News from the rep (Box 13)
- Letters from John Seigenthaler (Box 13)
- News release (Box 13)
- Various Clara (Box 13)
- Mead (Margaret Mead) interview (Box 13)
- New York Times, 1960 (Box 13)
- Pilgrimage (Box 13)
- The environment most “fit” our need (Box 13)
- Unknown Artist case 1 (Box 13)
- Catherine the great objects, 1190 (Box 13)
- Catherin the Great (Box 13)
- Faulkner Stuff (Box 13)
- The Tennessean (Box 13)
- The arts Academy (Box 13)
- Western Union (Box 13)
- Clara articles (Box 13)
- Russia 1 (Box 14)
- Russia 2 (Box 14)
- Russia 3 (Box 14)
- Russia 4 (Box 14)
- Russia’s Imperial City (Box 14)
- Catherine the Great (Box 14)
- Articles on problems in Russia (Box 14)
- Clara Trip to Russia (Box 14)
- Clara’s criticisms (Box 14)
- Beauty and beast show true love (Box 14)
- Art and entertainment (Box 14)
- Aesthetic realism (Box 14)
- Notes (Box 14)
- Clara, the Grandmother and critic (Box 14)
- Criticism and other random stuff (Box 14)
- Plays (Box 14)
- In the news (Box 14)
- Clara in the news (Box 14)
- The many facets and accolades of Clara (Box 14)
- Clara’s Mail (Box 14)
- Clara in the news (Box 14)
- Clara letter 1990s (Box 14)
- Clara’s work (Box 14)
- Letters to Clara (Box 14)
- Thomas Holt (Box 14)
- Clara article, 1973 (Box 14)
- London theatre flight (Box 14)
- London, 1984 (Box 14)
- London, 1985 (Box 14)
- London, 1980 (Box 14)
- Opinions by Clara, 1984 (Box 14)
- Art survey (Box 14)
- Discuss the non discussible (Box 14)
- London, 1986 and 1995 (Box 14)
- Control hospital (Box 14)
- In the news 1970s (Box 14)
- Stage plays Nashville public relations (Box 14)
- Art and reviews 1960 and 70s (Box 14)
- Clara photographs (Box 15)
- Australia (Box 15)
- Tennessee performing arts (Box 15)
- Clara letters 80s and 90s (Box 15)
- The year, 1994 (Box 15)
- Photos (Box 15)
- Clara’s resume (Box 15)
- Pictures (Box 15)
- News about Australia (Box 15)
- Belmont gallery (Box 15)
- Napoleonic era items (Box 15)
- Vanderbilt drama department (Box 15)
- Parthenon and the British Museum (Box 15)
- 1990 and 1992 letters (Box 15)
- U.S. General Service Administration (Box 15)
- Heart of Chronicle (Box 15)
- St. Andrew School (Box 15)
- In the Theatre (Box 15)
- Nashville letters (Box 15)
- Clara and Nashville (Box 15)
- Honorary degree for Clara (Box 15)
- Dialog (Box 15)
- Itinerary (Box 15)
- Clara notes (Box 15)
- Speaker Biographies (Box 15)
- Mail/ letters (Box 15)
- Rhode Island college (Box 15)
- Tennessee performing arts (Box 15)
- Nashville century (Box 15)
- Distinguish alumni (Box 15)
- Nashville (Box 15)
- Preservation of American Antiquities (Box 15)
- The Tennessean news letters and news papers (Box 15)
- Hieronymus letters (Box 15)
- House Award winner (Box 15)
- Clara Scholarship program (Box 15)
- Clara mail (Box 15)
- Austin Peay State folder (Box 15)
- Thank you, to Clara (Box 15)
- News paper clips, Clara’s career (Box 15)
- The Fourth of July letters (Box 15)
- Nashville and Clara (Box 15)
- Vanderbilt University (Box 15)
- Obituary and letters (Box 15)
- Clara the Tulsan critic (Box 15)
- Clippings (Box 16)
- Personal publicity (Clara) (Box 16)
- Monday etc (London Times) (Box 16)
- Brendan Beham (Box 16)
- London Theatre, 1986 (Box 16)
- Culture and ideas (Box 16)
- Performing Arts seminar (Box 16)
- Woman of the year (Box 16)
- Lift up the catch (Box 16)
- National design center (Box 16)
- Le petite salon (Box 16)
- London, 1985 (Box 16)
- London, 1979 (Box 16)
- Gloria (Box 16)
- Wonders (Clara) (Box 16)
- The challenge (Box 16)
- Art and life in (Box 16)
- Plays (Box 16)
- Vanderbilt and Vanderbilts (Box 16)
- Violet’s (Box 16)
- 1989 (Box 16)
- London, 1993 (Box 16)
- Monet (Box 16)
- Touchstone (Tennessee Humanities) (Box 16)
- Holiday (Russia) (Box 16)
- Various stuff (Box 16)
- 1994/ spring and fall (Box 16)
- London, 1992 (Box 16)
- Intermezzo (Box 16)
- Clara Hieronymus (Box 17)
- Better living, 1960 (Box 17)
- Clara pictures (Box 17)
- Articles by Clara 90s (Box 17)
- Clara articles 90s 2 (Box 17)
- Clara articles 90s 3 (Box 17)
- Clara articles 90s 4 (Box 17)
- Clara articles 90s 5 (Box 17)
- Clara articles 90s 6 (Box 17)
- Miscellaneous (Box 17)
- 50s and 60s (articles by Clara) (Box 17)
- 50s and 60s (articles by Clara) 2 (Box 17)
- 50s and 60s (articles by Clara) 3 (Box 17)
- 50s and 60s (articles by Clara) 4 (Box 17)
- Better living (Clara), 1958-1962 (Box 17)
- Art and theatre and an article about Clara (Box 17)
- Better living 1960s (Box 17)
- Clara – Tennessean-1960s (Box 17)
- Better Living with Clara-, 1961 (Box 17)
- Better living 1960s 2 (Box 17)
- Tennessean 1960s (Box 17)
- The Tennessean 1960s 2 (Box 17)
- The Tennessean 1960s 3 (Box 17)
- The Tennessean 1960s 4 (Box 17)
- 1966 script (Box 17)
- News 1950s and 60s (Box 17)
- The Tennessean 1950s (Box 17)
- Tennessean 50s and 60s (Box 17)
- The Tennessean, 1968 (Box 17)
- NY Herald Tribune, 1959 (Box 17)
- 1960 New York Times (Box 17)
- New York Times 19602 (Box 17)
- Motorist (Box 17)
- Home furnishings continue (Box 18)
- The early 60s (Box 18)
- More 1960s news from the New York Times (Box 18)
- News clips 60s (Box 18)
- News, the 60s continued (Box 18)
- In the news 60s (Box 18)
- Glover article (Box 18)
- Scripts and more (Box 18)
- National Council of the Arts and the New York times (Box 18)
- Art in the New York Times (Box 18)
- 1959 Tennessean (Box 18)
- Scripts and the Tennessean (Box 18)
- The year, 1959 (Box 18)
- 1960 (Box 18)
- 1960 news (Box 18)
- New York Herald, 1961 (Box 18)
- Chicago sun Time and other early 1960 news stories (Box 18)
- 1960 New York Herald (Box 18)
- Gusen heim and “the miracle worker” (Box 18)
- 1957 Tennessean and 1960 New York Times (Box 18)
- Random Clara news (Box 18)
- Clara articles 90s (Box 18)
- Travel and visits (Box 18)
- Clara letters (Box 18)
- Clara introduced/ or introduced by Clara (a person) (Box 18)
- Notes (Box 18)
- Sam Tarpley (Box 18)
- News Clips Album 1 (Box 19)
- News Clips Album 2 (Box 19)
- News Clips Album 3 (Box 19)
- News Clips Album 4 (Box 19)